assetbar.com 2010-10-14

# Privacy Notice - Assetbar

Welcome to our fun-filled privacy section!

**Cocoluna Inc., dba Assetbar**. ("Assetbar") recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, want to know what's up with privacy. Assetbar provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using any of the Assetbar Sites. 

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Assetbar Terms of Use. Your use of the Assetbar Sites and any personal information you provide on the Assetbar Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use. 

Please note that any video, image, profile information or other content posted at the direction or discretion of Users onto the Assetbar Sites becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice. 

### The Information Assetbar Collects

**User Provided Information:** You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to Assetbar when choosing to participate in various activities on the Assetbar Sites such as rating content, uploading images, uploading videos, writing notes, or posting messages in our comments section or in our private comments section. 

**Cookies Information:** When you visit the Assetbar Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Assetbar uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, the Assetbar Site may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

**Log File Information:** When you use the Assetbar Sites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

###  The Way Assetbar Uses Information

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Assetbar Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Assetbar Sites. 

Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you register or upload videos or photos or send messages through the Assetbar Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any photos, videos or content that you submit to the Assetbar Sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Assetbar Site changes or for customer service purposes). 

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Assetbar Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. Hopefully we improve the site and don't make it suck worse. 

We use cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Assetbar Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor individual and aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (d) track your entries, submissions, views and such. 

###  When Assetbar Discloses Information

Other members of the internet community may see your profile information or picture in a way that is consistent with the use of the site. For example, An image that is posted on a 3rd party site may include a link to the "details" which contains the public picture, the author's name, creation time, number of assets, as well as the number public and private views. If another assetbar member visits your public profile page, they may see all the intersections, or matches of the profile elements that you both share. 

We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

We may share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, asset views, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Assetbar Sites. 

We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 

Assetbar also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that Assetbar believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Assetbar, our Users or others. 

###  Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Assetbar Sites, in which case Assetbar may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. Please note that media files uploaded or created by Users to the Assetbar Sites cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

Please contact Assetbar via email or available web forms with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices. 

###  Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

Assetbar is currently ad-free, but in the future we may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Assetbar Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Assetbar Sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

Assetbar does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Assetbar to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed pieces of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Assetbar Sites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. 

###  Our Commitment To Data Security

Assetbar uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Assetbar and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Assetbar makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If Assetbar learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Assetbar may post a notice on the Assetbar Sites if a security breach occurs. 

###  Our Commitment To Childrens' Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Assetbar does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Assetbar Sites from persons under 18 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 18. If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use or access the Assetbar Sites at any time or in any manner. If Assetbar learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 18 years of age has been collected on the Assetbar Sites, then Assetbar may deactivate the account and/or make the submissions inaccessible. And always, think of the children! 

### Special Note to International Users

The Assetbar Sites are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Assetbar Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Assetbar Sites, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. 

###  In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that Assetbar is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the (hopefully) unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 

###  Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Assetbar Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions. 

**Date Last Modified:**  
This Privacy Notice was last modified December 1, 2007.
